Sunpreet Kaur

Senior Content Writer



SKILLS



SUMMARY

Seeking a tenure track position with a well-established employer, where I can contribute to the development of the organization through my technical skills, education and work experience.

I'm an expert writer, editor, and proofreader with more than six years of experience. From crafting promotional as well as informational text for various B2B and B2C clients, I've been into diverse content writings that includes (Web Content, Blog posts, User guides, Online Reputation Management (ORM), Articles, Press releases, Product descriptions & reviews, Website & app reviews, PPT, Infographics, eBooks, White papers, Company profiles, Brochure, ads, Case studies.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Mar 2023 - Content Writer Jan 2023 - Shine Logistics, Mohali

- Worked with internal and external teams to develop and execute content strategies.
- Created well-researched and stimulating content for informational and promotional content (training modules, speech, video content, blogs, brochure, and web content).
- Worked collaboratively with different teams to meet and exceed project goals.

Jul 2020 - Content Lead Mar 2022 Feliz Web Solutions, Mohali

- Led a team of 5 writers to develop blog content for the company website collectively as well as marketing materials for business partners.
- Researched and created interesting content for a variety of clients for websites, third party websites and social media platforms.
- Worked one-on-one with clients to understand their content needs and goals.
- Developed content strategies to assure desirable outcomes.
- Created content that accurately reflected clients' services and offerings.

Jul 2019 - Content Writer Jul 2020 Master Software Solutions, Mohali

- Manage and track company needs to ensure effective deployment of new projects in COVID
- -Ensure quality of Marketing and Creative briefs
- Dedicatedly pitch new ideas to solve business challenges
- Curated new ideas to publish the blogs on website, third-party websites, case study, etc,
- Published unique B2B and B2C content related to healthcare, delivery software, finance, SaaS based products, cryptocurrency, and technology while maintaining high productivity and high quality content.

May 2017 -Oct 2018 Content Writer

Soft System Solution, Mohali

- Worked on PPt, infographics, blogs, articles and web content for US based clients.
- Published blog content on diverse niches such as lawyers, immigration, beauty and wellness & healthcare, trucking, technology, core electric & electronic industry, ORM, healthcare & beauty, dentistry, fashion industry, travel, insurance company and many more
- Wrote technical and non-technical content for B2B and B2C clients

Jan 2016 -May 2017 Content Writer

Feliz Web Solutions, Mohali

Responsible for writing content and copies for various clients including but not limited to-

-website copy

-emails

-product descriptions

-blogs & articles

EDUCATION

Aug 2013 -Aug 2015 M.tech: CS

Chandigarh University

Aug 2008 -Jul 2012 B.Tech : ECE

Punjab Technical University

73%

CGPA: 5.6